two rounds of diving to come and this is
how it stands as we head into the final
stage of this competition Tonya couch
leads still for Great Britain with a
really good score but it's the second
page where all the action is because the
top 12 of 20 go through to the final in
this men women's 10 metre platform and
at the moment it's Green anger gamma of
Lithuania that has dived herself into a
qualification zone Germany's Christina
arson great start and a little wobble
then a brilliant comeback so the 16 year
old looking good for a place in the
final for three and a half then for
Round four it's a lot of rotation in the
pike position and you it she had to
leave this dive spinning a bit longer
than she wants hit and ran out of room
classic mistake jumps forward but here
she pulls in and suddenly it picks up
the rotation and she was surprised by it
and came out to Lane 49 500 sat in one
of those rotating off his chairs put
your arms and legs out and rotate it
you'll go around quite slowly and what
you're doing that then put your arms and
legs in fast and watch your increased
rotation and that's basically the
physics that are working here by the way
don't hurt yourself while you're doing
it but you Cove up needs a recovery dive
here arm stand forward two somersaults
single twist lovely understand
that's a classy dive from start to
finish I like to start their hips
forward flick off and then the twist and
then the line up if she bends her arms
that's the right way to go just a little
bit low though with the head I'm past
the board at the entry that's important
into the 60s
perchik over should climb a couple of
places with that one geography like
Amish then talked about this twister for
her during the course of the competition
is this the dive that he's going to be a
problem because she has a lot of heavy
black tape around her neck let me so put
the head under pressure
oh it's kept the head in place
beautifully done
yeah no wobble at all that's a brilliant
twist that's the way to do it a slight
over twist going through the water I
think because the dive is so pretty
they're not on the mark too many points
off might just keep it under 60 57 400
little core mas okay that's good I think
should maintain her qualification
position with one round to go no
problems so far though in terms of
qualification for Great Britain's Tonya
couch first position for the last couple
of rounds back two and half somersaults
one and a half twists in the pike
position then for Tonya in round four at
3.2 will most definitely be a medal
contender come deceive me because she is
gonna be in the final yeah very strong
takeoff just a little loose with the
legs going through the water good twist
reasonably strong Paul in on the Mike
[Applause]
loving this all the schoolchildren in
for this afternoon's session enjoying
the fact that couch keeps getting the
scores that keep putting number one
beside her name and that's what the fans
are enjoying now Christina shesh Gert
doesn't look like she's enjoyed her
competition I'm afraid the young Belarus
diver back three and a half somersaults
in the tuck position this is a big dive
this is joint most difficult dive in the
competition and the way she's been
diving Chris you don't hold out much
hope really now Georgia Ward did the
back three and a half and went short on
the entry
oh well she just about got there well
done and I was a real struggle the heads
in the wrong position is spinning slow
and are very untidy as she kicks out and
the huge twister in the water
forty four five five I think the fact
that she's safely down more important
but shesh get won't be heading to the
final
it's a fear writing year if she wants to
go to a European Championship final here
in London then she has to hit this dive
and she has to hit her final round dive
as well both at 2.84 verse two and a
half she's 35 points out of twelfth
place
No and that is probably it I'm afraid
for Sofia for today that's a poor dive
jumps forward she feels slow in the spin
so she's over compensated by staying the
Tuck longer also she has a problem
spotting on this knife she doesn't see
the water before kicking out
[Music]
fairly passive response at the moment
but she will be very disappointed
expected to see Sofia in the final but
not happening I'm afraid for the 26 year
old Hungarian arm stand back to
somersaults with one and a half twist
then for Laura Marano
of France she finishes with two twisting
dives both at 3.2 and she is on her way
at the moment to the final
good position
yeah good dive from Murano so that'll be
fine
she gets to jump off the platform yeah
good jump just a little and sighs being
scrappy with her feet though they're the
feet apart and then we come apart again
here 57600 though he's gonna be
absolutely fine for Laura France still
going along well with both divers 16th
place for Eleniak if she wanted a place
in the top 12 today she knew that every
single dive to be as good as she could
make it she's been just back off her
best so these last two rounds of vitals
she might need another diver to miss as
well if she's going to qualify she's 33
points out of top 12 so close she'll be
disappointed with the entry because it
was all going well just everything's to
slow though finished about three and a
half meters off the water need to finish
a lot higher than that good position in
front of the ears and so the water is
splashed off the top of their head just
52.2 Oh then for Ellen qualification
remains in doubt
moustache look it's been around about
the 9th position for the whole of the
competition the 20 year old Ukraine
diverse so it's looking at a place in
the final back to and half somersaults
in the pike position then at 2.9 but
there's no room for error here for
Hannah
yeah it's a good dive under pressure was
it sure she was going to make that with
that leave off the platform oh and she
jumped she didn't extend her legs her
legs are bent but the pike here on the
second part the dive was good and then
disappears I'm a lot better as well
nicely pointed so judges like that fifty
six five five and that should protect
crust no slicks place at the moment
Georgia Ward had one little blip in her
program they were popular with the crowd
the British divers but she's recovered
nicely from her blip round four then
forward three and a half whipped over at
the end as well and we'll see what the
judges do with this
oh what a take-off it was brilliant she
finishes so high there's the double
coming around one more I don't think she
was used to such a great takeoff that
was superb well unfortunately entry so
important 46 5 Oh Georgia Ward he's
gonna have to find her best in the last
round if she wants to qualify for this
evening's final that'd be such a shame
if she missed out because she is clearly
a talent and could definitely put
pressure on for the medals 15th position
at the moment for Celine Van do and have
done some great work to get into the top
12 rows as high as 11 and then a Miss in
the last round so this arm stand back to
somersaults with one and a half twists
has got to be good little too quick out
of that one and a little too splashy
going through the water I'm not sure
this will improve her situation very
lucky on the end here gets the push but
late into the twist
just gets the hands for water but not
fully locked out no they'd liked it
she'll take that any day of the week 62
for oh she was expecting to turn round
and see a mid 50 score there but Celine
van Duren is still in business and
really took sent in last place at the
moment some personal girls will have
been set for today's performance it'll
be a all about score $2 left then to
prove herself in would two and a half
and what about better dives today yeah
she was this would be the highest
scoring dive she hasn't got above 13 on
the first board dives three dives
pulling in hard but then breaking
position feet going flat before lining
up 82 marks 42 there we go
took something rather solemn look back
to the scoreboard as we go back to the
top of our leaderboard with Maria Cujo
back to and her off somersaults in the
pipe position then for the German a
little bit like back key today she's
kind of slid under the radar just gone
about her business and has been solid
and okay not at best but that's still
heading towards qualification yeah it's
been very consistent first I have sixth
place and in second then third this will
keep her up in the top five or six yeah
no problems 56 5 5 quick check with the
coach about their view on that
particular dive but that's fine Lilia
Pocock shook with the big names you're
never far away from a dive that just
establishes exactly where they are in
the pecking order and in the last round
Pro coccyx sent out a little message to
the rest of the field if you want gold
it's me you got to be great diving to
recover arm stand back three somersaults
in the Tuck position at three point
three big dive and a big score coming a
really big score coming I think she's
about 75 76 points behind Tonya couch
and this 3 3 is gonna definitely be in
the 70s
strong kick-out great reach back
oh look at that 75 9 oh and Prokop choke
reclaims the lead from Tonya couch at
the top of the leaderboard there's just
naught point 1 5 in it between Prakash
Chuck and couch and the likes of Kuya
Melina and bat key all through but it's
this part of the leaderboard that were
interested in anger Alma hangs on to
12th position Georgia Ward has improved
placing to 13th for Great Britain but
this final round of diving is going to
be very tense indeed a rendus li
difficult competition to qualify through
to the final 20 divers 12 places
available off the women's 10 metre
platform for this evening's final know
me back key next onto the board should
be going there for Italy without any
dramas but there's a lot of drama around
position 12 at the moment Italy then for
a place in the final and the 28 year old
she won't be pleased with that dive but
she'll be appearing tonight to compete
for medals
yeah jumps away from the platform cuts
off the height and another diver
finishing loads of water but she was in
fish and she will dive better in the
final former European champion back in
2011 to 84 though that's a comfortable
qualification and she and mum Boyet will
be going away to have a chat about how
they put that dive list together for
this evening's final back to the other
end of the leaderboard and Isabelle font
Essen of Sweden this is about signing
off in style and coming away with a
positive dive she won't be going to the
final
but she has benefited from the
experience and again another diver going
a long long way down the pool and away
from the platform yeah just it's the
technique if you haven't got the right
timing on the jump and momentum of the
run down the board just drags you
forward high score so far is 46 there we
go
an improvement and a positive forty
seven eight five but still under the 200
mark across five rounds of diving
Christina Russ and shouldn't be a
problem for her sixth position at the
moment finishes with this back twister
at 3.2 and on occasion the German has
looked really good
and she will be trying to dive like that
all the way through the final this
evening it's a good strong finish
beautiful twist and she knows the end
she again she will be pleased with this
she finished 15th last year had a
terrible competition and didn't make the
final first diver over 300 is Cristina
Vasan another 70 score for her and the
smile confirms a place in the final so
Germany should qualify to through Russia
still in doubt as to whether they can
qualify both their divers Petra Cova is
there hope now seventh position after
four rounds final dive back two and half
somersaults with one and a half twists
and that will be a Katarina through to
the final again not our best by any
means but safe enough same thing bends
the knees and the hips go back so it's
jumping backwards into the twister
rolling up and it makes it hard to pull
into the pipe after 26 3 5 yeah slightly
better than back keep still not into the
300s pressure dive then for young
revealer comas we'll have seen her great
friend Sofia Risinger miss her last
round so no she's Hungary's only chance
again toes mighty tight to the end and
she's gone right over on the finish and
she might have blown it with this dive I
don't think she's gonna make 270 she was
in 10th place good three and a half at
this point but then out way too late oh
dear
253 100 and it looks like both
Hungarians are going to miss out this
evening well that's a real shame
[Applause]
Britta now still with the chance of
qualifying to new couch has been in top
spot for most of this competition just
been surpassed by prokop chick in the
last round but couch to finish strongly
and to go through to the final as one of
the gold medal favorites that's the
entry of the day that's the best reverse
two-and-a-half was seen in the
competition jam strong spots the water
heats tire reaches back she squeezes
their ears and all the splash goes down
with her what a message to send out
another 70 score for couch and three
forty five to zero
that's a brilliant performance
christena church gap for Belarus has
been a little nervy up there hasn't
found our best form but has still
managed to turn in a reasonable score
but from 17th he's outside the
qualification zone
but we'll take a positive finish away
from this prelim legs a little bit messy
at the top but the entry was fine yeah
shouldn't I be just working on adding an
extra twist to that half twist good pipe
position didn't grab her hands correctly
she grabbed a wrist two 28-0 so
confirmation that gesture will not be
going through to the final but she says
cheerio with a smile nice final dive
from her a tough position for Sofia
Risinger to be in the twenty
six-year-old one of the most experienced
divers at this prelim competition but
knows that this dive is a dive to
nothing because she won't be going
through to the final this evening back
one and a half somersaults then with two
and a half twists to finish for Sofia
oh that's an incredibly frustrating
competition and finished for her she'll
just have to look back on the bronze
from the synchro competition here and
enjoy that and she'll be disappointed
with the entry because the dye of itself
was very good she lifted the chest up on
the entry and dropped a little short -
oh seven eight oh
and that is way off right injures
ability score is three ten hundred
points less than she's capable of doing
not a great day at the office for either
of the Hungarian divers Laura Marano
then at 22 years of age just coming into
peak zone for platform divers got the
experience got the skills certainly got
the degree of difficulty on the dive
list and proved it last year with that
silver medal and in with pre-capture can
couch and bat key and kuroky will go
through as one of the favourites for a
medal
okay little flutter with the feet and a
horrible entry means a Miss in the final
round but it would be good enough for
qualification that's so unusual
she didn't swing your arms up fast
enough so there's no rotation here tries
to pull into a tight Pike but it hasn't
worked just 40 marks 271 five Oh
and now Moreno is gonna have to wait and
see I thought she was safely home and
dry there
this is incredibly tight around position
to have around that bobble act then she
caused a problem a little bit too low to
the water there as she came out the
Swede there's a good final diet that
she's too far back on shore to get into
the top 12 the moment you just don't
know where this competition
well the bobble looks like it's gonna be
around about that 270 mark which is a
lake along Yee of France 278 5 everybody
above that might just be safe but you're
never sure until the competition is
finished 238 to 0 Eleniak won't be going
through that's one thing we can be sure
pal across nice look here in 8th
position there are no guarantees in this
prelim and that battle for top 12 is
going to be tight to 70 or around there
are all in with the chance the
concretion oh look push everybody down
one position here with this dive reverse
two-and-a-half somersaults then Frawley
ukraine diver all very slow spin but
she's done the right thing at the end
there Chris and managed to get it into
the water
yeah she slipped forward off the ball
finished very low I was looking at the
scores to be safe I was reckoning around
she needs 48 50 points
she's just about what I think yeah she
has she's fine
278 won oh so crushed nosh look goes
into the top 12 and that will just bump
everybody down a position that puts
Yulia Tymoshenko and to tenth and Kalani
down to ninth Moreno as well in 8th from
271 five-oh which leaves the door wide
open for this young lady 20 year old
George award from Great Britain with a
good degree of difficulty on this inward
three and a half this for a place in the
final just out of sync on that entry but
this is going to be really tight maybe
around 58 points will get her into the
top 12 just like it the judges like it
278 15.5 ahead of crush noise look and
that looks like Georgia warden Tonya
couch in the final for this evening's
competition for Great Britain all the
pressure passing down the line saline
van Duren now for the Netherlands in
11th place but this is by no means a
guaranteed place in the final back two
and a half somersaults in the pike at
two point nine this has to be really
good to make it aa good response to the
pressure but the splash might be an
issue here needs to get over the 15th
know about 48 points 50 points I'm not
sure will she get it
exchange she's cool all the water on the
back of the shoulders oh I think she's
done just enough to seventy four to five
puts ran doing in at seventh place just
ahead of Vanguard armor Marino and
Kalani mathematically she will go
through she's fine
and if it tooks and then we can take her
a little break from the drama of
qualification because took some won't be
going to the final so this is about a
positive finish to the competition big
dive for her the back twister at three
point two
oh and she's done it well great finish
yeah a little wobbly on the end good
twist the pike a little untidy going
from the twist now into the pike legs
aren't really locked out toes could be a
bit more pointed so just over the 200
mark for took sin but no qualification
to the final
so two divers to come to finish off this
10 metre competition and then we will
know our top 12 to go through from the
20 this afternoon and both of them
should qualify Maria Kuchar first for
Germany then Lily apricot Chuck for
Ukraine and it's not great I'm afraid
from courage Oh fortunately for her she
was way up the leaderboard ahead of this
dive no jump finishes low washes over
her feet flat
that was a poor diet she was in third
but she needed 595 points to go ahead of
Tonya she was two points
she's fine so Kojo 294 five five is
through to the final it signs off with a
kiss last diver defending champion Lily
apricot Chuck will bump Kalani
out of the top 12 for France but Laura
Marano is going to hang on in 12th
position
assuming that precook just gets the
score out of this dive slightly
ponderous back twister but what an entry
she beats 70 1.30 to go ahead of Tonya
couch and it's a high degree of
difficulty good twist there pulls him
really well because of the entries
a little bit wobbly I'm not sure she
hasn't got it no second place that means
Tonya couch does win the prelims and
will go through as the favorite for gold
to this evening's final but that's going
to be one heck of a shootout between her
and the defending champion and let's not
forget that whole host of names to
factor in the likes of Kershaw and bat
ki will be there Christine of us and
going really well both Germans in 3rd
and 4th Pacheco has made it through
Jorge award brilliant finish to qualify
in 7th position so Great Britain have
two competitors through but here's the
important facts timoshkin ena has missed
out and Kalani does hang on for the 12th
place Laura Mariner in 11th and France
do qualify to through but that is a very
tight competition it's going to be a
brilliant final
the divers being introduced to a
fantastic crowd here at the London
Aquatic Center at this evening for the
winnings 10 meter final when he occurs
EUR for Germany just making her way out
certainly amongst the favorites followed
by her compassion what a great
performance she was 17 year old in the
prelims Christina Batson to get through
in third place and to follow Christine
and the two big guns in tonight's
competition the courtship looking pretty
cool the Ukraine defending champion
looking to make it another win to add to
the four that she already has on this
apparatus and can Tonya couch do it
tonight
brilliant performance in the prelims
from the British girl and Tonya couch
comes into this final as marginal
favorite but that's going to be a very
good shootout to watch between prokop
cook and couch Simon Golding and former
Olympian euro sport diving expert Chris
snowed alongside me for you coverage
this evening from the diving Paul to
great events to look forward to the
first one I should be very interesting
indeed they're women's ten Mitra is
always interesting but the standard was
so high this morning you had to get 270
just to make the top 12 normally is 250
and there was a blinding performance
from Sonia never had a medal in the
individual Europeans on 10
before and she'd be the reigning
champion pro culture they both averaged
70 points and it could go even higher
today and to put that into context in
terms of the points for the gold and how
that compares with the Chinese with Rio
just around the corner well if you take
Chenery Lin in 2008 she averaged 89
point for a dive world record of 437
points yes put it into context but
tonight it's all about the European
Championship and the winner of the next
gold medal in the women's 10 metre
platform competition as I said Tonya
couch for the home nation comes in as
marginal favorite and she's got George
Award for company who has a very good
dive list indeed she has a degree of
difficulty that could get her a medal
but there's a whole host of athletes
that could be on the podium by the end
of this one
- our divers have qualified through from
the prelim competition of 24 this
woman's 10 metre platform file on the
first of two gold medals on offer in the
diving pool on day five of the 2016
European Aquatics Championships and they
go right up to the highest platform in
this fabulous diving arena to contest
gold medal number eight Tonya couch for
Great Britain was in superb form in the
prelims but all of the divers it has to
be said did miss a dive so we've always
got that potential for this event to be
turned on its head if someone who misses
misses with a very low score
we hope that doesn't happen this evening
on Friday the 13th we hope that we get a
very good contest for the gold medal
France have qualified two athletes
through a lie Kalonji
is going to be the first diver the 18
year old she'll be followed straightaway
by her senior compact reott laura marano
who took silver last time out but for
Kalonji this is very much a step up to
the senior level and she's going to open
with an inward two and a half
somersaults at 2.8 and that's a fine
stop soon as she was on the end she
sprung off it's the entry that was
impressive those springy jump good line
up because there's hardly any splash
fantastic pike there she's gonna score
really well yes they roll on the end
just maybe one or two degrees oh alright
so this is a sign of things to come in
terms of scoring coach by Frederic
Pierre
and you'll see the coach is interacting
with the divers on a constant basis
they've been new to the sport of diving
here on Eurosport that's a normal
feature the divers get feedback
constantly from the coaches and very
much encourage it as well and as soon as
that's happened then they go off and
start to visualize for the next round of
dives which means the camera operator
has to follow them so that we can get
score graphic up at some point we will
have it in a moment for you I can tell
you based on what we've heard in the
background from the judges scores it's
gonna be a good one it will be a good
one she got 61 in the prelims and this
is far superior in any moment now
but I think this is gonna be a cracking
opening score for LA Kalonji
well in an entry like that the divers
worth at least eight maybe even more had
no space whatsoever
now I still predict it's gonna be an
average of 70 or more to win this
contest so if any of the girls can get
close to that throughout there they're
gonna get gold silver or bronze and
that's not far off is it 67 to 0 from
Kalonji good start from the French
number 2 and we turn to the French
number 1 for the next dive Laura morrow
not in would three and a half
somersaults in the top position at 3.2
she might be diving as the 11th
qualifier but she has the scoring
capability and the tariff on the dives
to make a big impression this evening
and remember prelims score goes out the
window this is back to square one
Maryland for France in wood three and a
half in the tuck position
it's a mess and this is what the contest
could come down to tonight Chris if you
do miss its by how much you miss those
disastrous you win 72 points in the
prelims there though she fell out of it
out too late a little bit close with her
hair coming around on the first
somersault there's that miss there
doesn't pick up the water on the triple
neither's found the spot the water come
out quick silver medal last year well
this was as Chris said 72 in the prelims
this will be closer to 27 it's certainly
not gonna make it into the 50s remains
to be seen if she can make it into the
40's she can 49:6 doe so Mariano gets
off to a poor start on the 2015 silver
medalist in this event under pressure
already
now what a refreshing change this young
lady was earlier today 17 year old
Genevieve green under Army from
Lithuania but actually left with you
only when she was 2 years of age and has
done all of her diving in the USA trains
alongside World Championships synchro
finalist Cassidy cook and a horrible
inward two and a half to start I'm
afraid and you heard the crowd groan
this has gone badly wrong yeah it's
right on us on the start she slips right
here oh she is so lucky that that didn't
go badly badly wrong for her yeah she
slips and you just there was nothing to
push against
she was actually lucky that her feet
didn't hit on that first somersault as
well that would have stopped her
completely there she's smiling she's
unbelievable that's uh felt like yeah
still smiling away whole competition to
go but has to accept a sub 20 mark I'm
afraid for that openness so an Jian army
having made the final big day for her
that was a huge result unfortunately
hasn't got the star she wanted in the
final itself next up from the
Netherlands Celine van dune 23 years of
age now starts with a bang twister so
back two and a half somersaults with one
and a half twists in the pipe position
you just heard in the background the
announcer here in the stadium just
letting everybody know that there is an
input issue with the scouring pads we've
had the odd electronic gremlin during
the course of this week Chris but it's
to be expected it's a very complex
system then they go to flip cards the
old system back to the good old days yes
I think that's when colour telly was
just being invented as well it's always
a bit of fun to see that let's hope that
they do manage to fix the problem
quickly because we all enjoy seeing the
graphics come up the split of all the
marks from all the judges that's it
tremendously helpful from everyone's
point of view it's really hard to use
the flip cards nowadays because they
blinker the judges so in between each of
the judges there is a screen and you
can't look across that also means that
the judge is closest to the recorders
table won't be able to see anything that
the judges put up and there's three of
them over there and there's four on the
far side where the 3-meter springboard
while it's thrown the judging committee
in the panel into a bit of turmoil and
they're all now holding up the cards on
the main table holding up the cards for
the judges to say look this is what
we've got to go to we've got to go to
the old paper system so electronics at
the moment look to be out the window
this is not good for Saline Vanda and
incidentally it's okay if you're not up
there on the steps or up there on the
board yeah you can take a little bit of
a pause but if you're already up there
then this is a very touchy moment and if
you haven't got your competition
underway either as well then this is
going to take a little bit of mental
toughness to get through this period and
it's the first round as well as over
when they get wet well we had already
got confirmation of that mark from
unguent army there it is again
19600 unfortunately no reprieve she
would just be very grateful that nothing
else went wrong with that dive because
once that foot slipped away she could
have been in real trouble so time at
last for Saline run down that back
twister that I described at 3.2 she's
got three dives that go into the three
so not a bad dive list from the 23 year
old Dutch woman
and well considering the weight that was
a pretty good effort yeah very good
effort I did think she was gonna write
over on the end but she didn't she
controlled the entry here's the job that
was good
only a little bit away from the platform
one and a half twist now that's the hard
bit pulling force into the pike
just a small wobble there the splash had
been thrown up because her hands not
flat enough from the water but
technically a good dive in the prelims
she only went 50 points this is far
better yes sixty five six oh great
opener I'm not the only person that had
to wait for us nice look of Ukraine
would have been halfway up the steps
waiting to go in with two and a half
somersaults then for her that's a very
good synchro record and as done well
with Janko in the past but on an
individual basis still looking for that
first big result just outside the medals
last time around in fifth position she
has a little problem with flattening the
feet off she did it in the prelims as
well but the dive overall is still good
yeah in the prelims she was close this
isn't close didn't need to flatten her
feet I think it's more of a habit now
that was a really good take on just need
to keep those toes pointed she would
have been all right good entry though so
there's only maybe ten centimeters of
splash it's gonna be a good score
it is a good score 63 Oh Joker even
income with a bit of advice and listen
to this reception from the home crowd
for the home athlete Georgia Wars diving
in her home pool this is where she
trains along with Tom Daley and coach
Jane Figueredo already has a bronze
medal from this european championships
in the team event with matty lee and has
a massive dive list she starts with the
back twister
it's okay it's okay in terms of degree
of difficulty Chris she has got a dive
list that can rival anyone yes there's
three divers doing back three and halfs
daughters one of them well this is
better than the prelims it went really
over in the prelims this is just
slightly over but technically strong I
wonder if she'll be strong enough
eventually to do to no harm Tris
she's a great diver she's already proved
that show good resilience this morning
to come back from a bad start but that's
a good start better than the 64 marks
George award in good shape
[Applause]
Noemi back here there in 28 years of age
alongside Pocock cook the most
experienced athlete in this field she's
won this title before she's not gonna
win it again with dives like that I'm
afraid a poor forward three and a half
somersault opener she's really high well
it's the problem she's also jumped
forward so although she has come out
late from the pike Mike here is good but
she is traveling forwards hard to stop
the rotation and she reaches the wrong
part of the water needed reached more
forward towards the one metre boards on
the far side
just 45 marks from bat key and in this
sort of company you can't afford those
errors I talked about the fact that
there are going to be misses and it's by
how much you miss but 45 is probably too
too much she's gonna have to rely on
other athletes missing dives as well so
forward three and a half somersaults now
same dive from PG Cova of Russia the 19
year old coached by her synchro
partner's mother timber Shanina who saw
her daughter miss out in the prelims so
this is Russia's hope they'd say it's so
so it's not too bad entry but it was
very low so strong takeoff that was good
not traveling forwards just lining up in
front of the face going through the
water see see just the last minute the
feet kick she rolls under the water
brings some of it back a good jump at
the start this will be a decent Park
it's a good opener for her cheek over
and she has the lead by just a third of
a point from Ally Kalonji of France
two Germans to come next and always the
same in each rotation of these at five
rounds
Maria Kershaw already has a gold from
the synchro on the ten meter that's a
solid start from her nice entry good
forward three and a half there she did
something funny with her feet though
he's gonna throw the water good jump
spinning fast just the feet relaxing
right here which the judges will pick up
as she rolls her feet flattened
it's a shame she'll lose five six points
for that but another diver makes it into
the sixty points out George Oh at the
moment in fifth position doing very well
today to get through in third and fourth
but for Christine of us and this is
uncharted territory the student from
Berlin doesn't have any senior medals
yet in the European Championships could
today be the day inward three and a half
somersaults this is a big dive it was
the second highest scoring dive no it's
not gonna be far away again that's a
great start for Larson 75 points I think
the one in the prelims though the body
was just a little tighter springy jump
they're that small mistake everything
else though good squeeze in tight
spinning fast finishing high and it's
good in safe as well not too far or too
close 75
it's the final and the judges have gone
where they're brilliant diving from us
and and she opens once again with a 75
pointer to take the lead two divers to
come in round one luli apricot took the
defending champion looking to add a 5th
10 meter european championship gold to
her CV forward three and a half then in
the pipe position at 3.04 lule it's a
much better start than the prelims the
prelims only got sixes
different pike she holds right down the
bottom of her legs
has that gag going around but she got
the tearing rip sound good stop
beautiful point little movement so
she'll get much higher than sixes 75 to
old leads for Germany and Christina
arson and just underneath that at 72 for
a lower degree of difficulty that's a
fine opener from to capture once again
the decibel level goes up here in the
London Aquatics Center Tonya couch the
26 year old from Plymouth coached by
Andy banks to open her account in this
final same dive that we've just seen
from pro cock cook so a little bit of
pressure on couch here and that's the
way to respond maybe not quite as good
on the entry as Prokop shock but that
will certainly get her off to a great
start
yes it had a little bit more splash I
think this was superior slightly flat
feet and then pointed again coming out
at the splash I spot the judges might
mark a downfall oh wow that was that is
a tough call for Tonya couch 61 500 not
the start that she was looking for but
we told you it'd be interesting it's the
youngster 17-year old Christine of arson
that leads at the moment we'll take a
break there round 2 of the woman's ten
meter final on day five here at the
European diving championships on
Eurosport armstand back to somersaults
with a half twist for Ally Kalonji of
France
nicely done she started this competition
on fire
in fourth place qualified in 12 that's a
half twist first and then into the pike
but wobbly though with a loose back
going through the water good at this
point arms lining up in front have any
splash that doesn't really squeeze the
ears with the arms and lock the body out
for a degree of difficulty if just two
point seven is always gonna be tough to
get yourself into the 60s but solid
diving from her now Laura Marano has
already made her mistake a big mess in
round one that's out of the way
she now needs four rounds of world-class
diving if she wants a shot at the medal
forward three and a half somersaults in
the pike position then in round two for
Marren oh yeah it's better they're just
a little loose on their entry again the
technique is good what we're looking for
is upright and then the first part of
the Summerson to move and then drop so
there she gets it
Pike is near-perfect the face very
cushions pulling in hard second or third
somersault faster than the first because
the pikes tighter 63 marks for Mara no
may enable her to advance a position or
two this Chris note said seventies is
where you need to be this evening if you
want to get in amongst the medals and
take that gold now and your army
the Lithuanian a really scary start for
her she got away with it so for three
and a half somersaults in round two
oh my goodness me and it's going from
bad to worse I'm afraid for the
Lithuanian that is a poor dive and it's
a painful one there so on the inwards
she caught it on face
now a whole of the back completely slaps
so she misses her spot this is good
lovely tuck position and miss is it
doesn't see the triple divers feel the
trip will come around then they look at
the water and then they reach for it and
she just stayed in there tuck still
smiling unbelievable and hasn't made it
to thirty points yet let's just hope for
her sake that things improve Selim von
donate for the Netherlands 2.8 for this
next round inward two-and-a-half
somersaults then this is the dive that
Kalonji really nailed first up in this
final for France
what can Celine do
I'm very grateful through the air it
looked if anything a little easy for her
that's because she did all the right
moments the throw was at the right time
you had to coordinate the throw with the
jump pulls it straight away so she was
into the pike as tight as you can be
right at the beginning some of the
divers take half a rotation to get in
there little splashy on the entry 58 806
lean Ronda and score ticking along
nicely it's nicely before Ukraine the 20
year old will be performing a forward
three and a half somersaults in the pike
position at 3.0 this is actually her
highest degree of difficulty it was a
best dive in the prelims just whistle
confirmation that she's good to go
and she's got it so in her own time no
mister that's washed over again so well
the pressure coming to bear that little
bit of additional adrenaline and it can
make a huge difference to the dives
sometimes when you tighten up in a
competition things just don't flow she
hit the end of the diving board and she
didn't throw in time so the momentum of
the job down the pole has taken her out
she misses her spot pikas okay it's been
quite a few misses now
fifty-two 504 off but not quite there
opportunities opening up left right and
center here can Georgia Ward take a
chance she's got the dive list a high
degree of difficulty to do it back three
and a half somersaults in the Tuck
position at three point three the
toughest dive in the competition
damn Georgia what a dive I knew that was
coming
the last two attempts she was gone short
and I'm sure I coaches said keep your
feet up
don't kick them back to waterfall she
did that it's a reach back
and with three point three this is gonna
be a phenomenal score at the moment the
highest score is been 75 in the prelims
can she go 80 that response from the
crowd massive and she has done 80 point
eight five puts George award in the hunt
for gold
Noemi back heat for Italy three times
silver medalists in this event in 10 12
14 but she also won it back in 2011 so
the platform has been kind to the
Italian it would three and a half
somersaults then round two to make up
for that miss in round one for that and
put everything into the entry there was
a booming sound that she goes through
the water and that suckers really tight
as well
squeezing Jim very closer than these and
the boom goes around the whole of the
poolside brilliant diving from back key
now we're cooking another 80 look at
that and back he goes to 125 for second
place behind George award and that is
the way to send the message out to the
rest of this field
ekaterina picture cover then next for
russia in with three and a half
somersaults for her at 3.2 sheet she has
got a tough dive list as well everything
in the threes and she does the three
point three in the next round
oh it's great diving and it's
competition Chris has come alive these
are world-class dives
as we said in the earlier competitions
though the standard is high its Olympic
here everyone's been preparing very hard
since last September and he can see it
just a little sproule on the entry
that's bit of splash it's still good
dive brilliant 70 point 404 perchick
over and this one this competition is
warming up nicely Maria cause you're
they already has that gold medal with my
pan in the 10 metre synchro competition
but that was a little unexpected and in
the end the medal came due to some
misses by other teams but she'll take it
sport soldier by trade but currently
studying as a lon psychology student and
she's gonna need all of that experience
to put into this arm stand back to her
step
[Applause]
three point two degree of difficulty
okay she gets a push off her arms before
going into the one and a half twist
[Applause]
that's good there now horse forward
looks at the water lines up just in time
what water dive and that look fabulous
on that last slo-mo and that's a
fabulous score seventy six eight zero
taxes a one three nine eight oh five
point oh five off of the pace set at the
moment by the bridge or award Christine
of us and will always follow her job in
every round lovely start from the
seventeen-year-old another 75 would do
nicely
oh and it's not gonna happen there's the
mistake from worse and then washes it
over exactly the same as the prelims she
hangs onto the pipe too long the feet go
up to the 10-meter and over on her
stomach needs to be out now she's still
in the pike and she finished something
like five and a half meters there and
see the five meter boulders she's coming
out on to the wrong place tough break
for us sent thirty point four five
dumpster down to ninth place with two
still to come true Lily apricot check in
second position behind kawasan with her
seventy pointer in the first round much
better start than she made in the
prelims in with three and a half in the
tuck position now high degree of
difficulty looking for the big score yet
enormous score that's a fabulous dive
she's so high this is
hard died and she had so much time at
the end double there now she finished
above the five meter
we've already had 280 dives this is on
the same par who's George award
astonishing stuff in round 2 eights
another 1881 six outputs Brokaw took in
the lead so she will move ahead of
George award by eight point seven five
points
talk about pressure for Tonya couch blew
everyone away for most of the prelim at
an error at the end which led a few
athletes get closer to her but came into
this competition as the marginal
favorite and has to produce some magic
here
um stand back twister then she's in
business best rounds I've seen that
Europeans for a long long time
nails it among the highest score is 81.6
well our feet were better than the
prelims so this is going to be massive
yes it's gonna be 18 oh it's 86.4 back
in the second position at 147 9 oh and
just five points down on lowly apricot
Chuck what a competition a simple dive
for Alea Kalonji you'll see it on the
replay but unfortunately she has
problems with the reverse dive family
and has to stick to that a very simple
dive at 1.9 she's done it beautifully
again she has but because that load
degree difficulty all come up has a very
low score somewhere around 40 points she
would have gone even high over the score
she hadn't had that drift over at the
end 39 I know for Kalonji and that's the
dive that he's always gonna cause us
some problems until she builds some high
degree of difficulty in well Laura
Moreno must be wondering what they what
on earth is going on in this competition
because it's all happening around it has
not found a good dive as yet the French
woman who finished in second place in
2015 in Rostock and she would dearly
love to come to the party in round 3
with this back two and a half
somersaults
oh why not why not another brilliant
entry well maybe this is gonna be the
round where she starts to pick up good
jump looking with her head you can see
them head moving she looks at the end
the board sees it looks at the Walter
sees it reaches back and sees it and
disappears yes what a lovely way of
describing the process that the divers
going through Chris brilliant and that's
a good score seventy three nine five
four Laura Marano a little collision
with the camera operator but she's happy
wouldn't have been smiling if she got a
40 I can tell you now Genevieve and your
army keep your fingers crossed
Friday the 13th is a day that at the
moment she would prefer to forget no
it's it's still not happening I'm afraid
for Genevieve
well for the first three quarters of the
dive it's fine good jump spots well on
the first somersault but she doesn't
pick up the second spot here it's good
but right here she's looking in the
wrong place she should have seen the
water and then pushed the feet out she
leaves it too late it's gone over
well the smile once again
but it's looking a little tired now
33:35 still only managing to get to 62
marks of the three rounds of diving
sleeve and oh and then for three and a
half somersaults in the pike position at
3.0 diving well but the class around
here from some of the big names at the
moment eclipsing anything that she's
managed to do around three needs to be
big for the Dutch woman it's a good dive
little bit of a depth charge going up
after the entry but she'll take that
yeah this is correct she jumps up one in
prelim jumped forward but as she's
coming out the hole of the middle of her
body is low she's not holding the
stomach tight then that goes loose and
the water then hits you and you bonk
your body concertinas and that's why
this flash has come up
[Music]
still waiting for that mark than 58 500
that's as bad as it gets
then it's not gonna be too bad for
Celine Van doing but in this kind of
company at the moment it isn't good
enough
that's knowledge then next position
after two rounds forward twister so two
and half somersaults then with a single
twist let's see where she puts the
twists in to this particular dive
so the twist straight away and then
pulls into the somersaults and a nice
entry yeah just a small jump forwards
yeah she landed on the board a body bent
forward there and as she strained down
rather than forwards get some good entry
though just a little bit sloppy on those
at the start and just going into the
pike but have a little deeper pike
once again coach even encode comes
across rich at 60.9 Oh especially giving
a good account of herself
now George award you get the feeling
actually that it was Georgia that really
kicked this competition into life in
round two absolutely nailed her back
three and a half went into the lead and
everybody found it difficult to work
live with her from there so arm stand
back to somersaults with one and a half
twists for Georgia Ward in our home Paul
another good dive here and she is
definitely in business superb that
little separation of the legs as she
came away from the platform but got it
all back together yeah it's so minor
though it's not going to affect the
judges score the loose body going
through the water will drop her down low
of it
she went 67 points in the prelim this is
just about the same dive very good in
the air its splashy going through the
water so be a sinless 467 points will
keep her on track and that's where she
is 67 204 two hundred and twelve oh five
Ward moves back into the lead
[Applause]
do I be back key then form a Hungarian
diver that moved to Italy back in 2005
coached by mommy ball janosh the 1992
Olympian from Barcelona has been superb
in this competition in previous years
but isn't happening for at the moment
verse two and a half then follow me how
high did she go up the platform there
and always in control she didn't hold
back she's standing there she thought
about it she visualized it and then she
jumped she was kicking out seven and a
half meters a double here seven five
meters kick she floats around for six
meters there's the seven meter right
next to her and then she reaches back
dive into the 70s and remember that's a
lower degree of difficulty at two point
eight so that score is fabulous and mum
is happy Katarina perchick over then in
fifth position at the moment sometimes
in the shadow of her synchro partner Tim
Lucia Nina has a chance to shine here
because tamesha Nina failed to get
through the prelims so back three and a
half this is her toughest dive the equal
toughest dive in the competition oh it's
a nasty one so again another big miss
and this time it's from the Russian
missed it in the Prius only scored
40-something points on it the jump is
good mates spinning too slow she hangs
on as long as possible
and then goes over it's not accelerating
it's just dropping like a stone and
barely time to come out she'll be lucky
to get 40 on this one it was even worse
than the prelim yeah it's just 37 9 5
then for Pacheco but a real shame for
her and that's probably the metal
challenge done for the Russian but Never
Say Never
anything can happen we're platform
diving is concerned and it did in the
prelims few big names missing out a few
big names nearly missing out because
you're then the 27 year old German
trains in Berlin coach my young coach
Marc and that's really nice but on a day
she's a very tidy very efficient diver
and that's what she's bringing to this
final yes in finished in 12th place last
year but she's got three bronze medals
in this event from 1112 and 2013 it was
a good dive it's a lower degree of
difficulty I was watching her toes as
she passed the born it was just about
safe enough any closer and she would
have touched solid score 60 point 2-0 to
reach the 200 mark after three rounds of
five
slightly disconsolate from crostino
arson she went from first to 11th and
that's not gonna keep anyone happy
so vas an arm stand ID for her arm stand
back to somersaults one and a half
twists and that gives her a degree of
difficulty of three point two so this is
the kind of dive if she gets the entry
that she was getting in the prelims that
could put a back in contention it's good
it's good but it's not gonna push her up
too far on the leaderboard there's a
better handstand this time in the
prelims she didn't get to that
completely straight position now she is
just twisting all the way down to the
pool but it's an entry it's gonna score
really well technique isn't that
brilliant off the platform not enough
jump and the twist took so long to get
into 70 point four oh then takes it to
170 6:05 so she will improve her
position from eleventh ninth just a
reminder
Georgia Ward leads for Great Britain on
212 oh five pro cock cook and her
compatriot Tonya couch can get past her
and we're diving like this the defense
of her title is starting to look very
very good indeed that's a great dive on
that back to an R what a jump spots just
collapses a little bit going through the
water here it's good reaches back she
knows needs only 58 points to go into
the lead she'll get that
and the four-time European ten meter
champion moves back in the top spot to
2175 so that's a nine point seven
advantage over Georgia Ward in second
21.7 advantage over Maria Cujo in third
and Tonya couch has got this tough
position the pressure keeps passing down
inward three and a half then for Tonya
at three point two and she will keep
pace with that dive 73 points to go and
laid on I'm not quite sure with that
entry she pulls the chin down on the end
and but that starts good finishes high
but just lost it on the entry neither
had the confidence to keep stretching
she pushes here and you see the arms are
out of line so the judges will mark her
down for that
so probably sub 70 but by how much you
are just under five points so Tonya
couch does move into second at 2:13
five-o just ahead of Georgia Ward but
it's the defending champion Procop cook
that leads back just in time for another
rep entry this time from Laura Meredith
the French number one after that arm
stand back to somersaults and one and a
half twists another lovely entry using
the bend knee to flick off a lot of the
ladies are just cleaning off it smile
like that technique gets a little bit of
extra rotation and a fast twist but it's
a the entry little splash that's given
under 73 points ok moves to 260 15 after
that 73 6-0 so a couple of good rounds
there from Laura Marano
and she's kinda back in business but
needs to keep it at the highest possible
level if she's gonna be in with a shout
of a place on the podium
now come on Genevieve seventeen-year-old
from Lithuania Reverse two and a half
somersaults needs an entry needs to get
some confidence back
and it's just not gonna happen fallout
her this evening and you sometimes get
competitions like this Chris it doesn't
matter what you do it doesn't work
sometimes when you've got experience if
you're spinning at a different rate in
the competition you know to make
adjustments and that's what's happened
here she's jumped a little higher than
normal she's spinning faster than normal
but she's done the same kick out that
she would do in practice and that is why
she's gone over the extra gentleman she
hasn't taken into account it still a
high school student back in the USA but
retained her Lithuanian passport when
she moved there at two years of age and
has to put this one down to experience
I'm afraid this evening Selene valuing
has died very well and seventh the best
that she can manage at the moment this
then her joint toughest dive arm stand
back to somersaults with one and a half
twists so like her back twister in the
first round it's worth three point two
in terms of degree of difficulty is this
the dive that puts her back in business
not quite I'm afraid again just going
over on the end judges will certainly
deduct for that yeah not only did she
lean but she had the bent knee flick
which just gave her a little too much
rotation when she pikes down she
couldn't stop it digs their head in as
well actually accelerated those legs
going over
fifty-two a doe it is a Miss if I'm
doing will not be able to recover from
that so that's her metal challenge done
hand across nicely today for Ukraine
again dive very solidly but in this kind
of company paint the position the best
that she can manage at the moment
unlikely to match her fifth place from
2015 which was a brilliant performance
no it's very strange start to that back
two and a half yeah she keeps her knees
bent so right here a legs are bent and
then she finally straightens up those
legs for the second part of the diet but
that's an untidy Pike there here doesn't
spot the water that looks to me more
like a guest rather than using your eyes
to see where to come around where to
come out and she's going right over
to 19900 that rolling score and that's a
Miss of 43 five-oh Laura Marano leads
for France then on to 61 5 George award
will be looking to go past her and by
some distance with this fourth round eye
forward three and a half somersaults in
the pike position then her lowest degree
of difficulty this needs to be perfect
and again just washes over at the end
I'll she'll be frustrated with that
that's a real shame she only needed 48
points to go in the lead why she's got
such a good takeoff here pause him well
there needed to be out already
yeah now shift now their entry she's
getting an extra 15 points
oh yeah coach Figueredo watching on and
57 gives her the lead at 260 905 but
it's not the kind of advancement that
she was looking for we've had his George
Awards miss then okay she'll probably
take that one big dive to come in the
final round for her for knowing me back
key so far this has not been her
European Championships fifth position at
the moment so outside the medals but
still has the degree of difficulty to
force away onto the podium you need 70
points to catch George award
and that just was one of those classic
arms stand dives where the diver just
falls straight off the platform and into
the water she needs to go back in the
gym to work on this to get the timing
she just hasn't got the timing and
that's why it looks so awkward
as a Miss for her you can see how low
she finishes to the water not a great
dive to watch not a great score to get
54 for 0 bank his challenge falters
again
and Katerina Petrova one miss too many
and she's down in tenth position but in
this kind of competition and in this
kind of company one miss is too many
slightly different arm stand position
here facing the port with her back for
this two somersaults single twist at
three point one unusual dive this what
both she and Timothy Nina have the same
technique for the push off and it's
really effective
yeah the hips go first and then the feet
flick so there's the hips and then the
flip then the single twist and look at
the water there's a good technique maybe
just bending the arms a little too much
you only have to help relax your arms
rather than bend them right down it's
actually quite complicated diet
and that's a good score sixty-eight to
zero takes it a to 4405 so partial
recovery once again from perchick over
now Chris you think Maria Cujo could be
the danger back two and half somersaults
from her in the pike position yeah she
only needs 69 points to take the lead
and she went she actually missed this
dive in the prelims and he got 56 she's
got to remember to come out in time not
let the dive go over Iceland over has
done it again say almost carbon copy of
the prelims you should be able to make
an adjustment in the prelims if you're
gonna go short you have the same sort of
pressure because you wanted to make the
top 12 you need to remember to come out
early looks at the water too late it's
by pasture and out too late so right
over
[Music]
4205 and that miss I'm afraid he's going
to put the lid on cujo's challenge and
less others miss around her for Vasan
same situation as Kershaw except her
miss occurred on the last dive service
and trying to repair the damage with
this forward three and a half
somersaults in the pipe position that's
more like the entries we saw from her in
the prelims there's amazing that she
could get down with no splash even with
the dive going over so it's going to
score well yes you attach the end of the
diving board pulling him well here again
the technique of holding down on the
lower part of the ledge rather than
round the back of the knees it doesn't
matter if you get an entry like that
good awareness good scoop under the
water to save that dive and that's a
good score sixty-seven five oh it's
worse and temporarily up to fifth
position with two divers still to come
in this round I'm stand back three
somersaults in the tuck position four
lule prokop cook for the joint highest
degree of difficulty in the competition
at three point three this is the big
dive for her Chris if she gets this
right gold and defense of her title is
on it's only a seventy five point nine
in the prelims she only needs 48 points
to go ahead of Georgia
all right beautiful from procore Church
she has not missed a beat this evening
well as she gets 8 which is worth it's
going to be 75 again strong kick-out oh
this is even better than the prelims
look sharp kick reaches back tightens
her body quicksave under the water stops
the feet kicking over that's the way to
go through she's always known what she's
doing she saw that triple somersault for
about four meters up Chris node loved it
but more importantly the judges loved it
84 won five takes her over 300 305 900
leads she's just put 36 points between
her and Jorge award in second place and
she's done it again she's passed all the
pressure down the line to the 26 year
old Brit Tonya couch back twister them
for Tonya at 3.2 just to stay in touch
oh what a response from Tonya couch yeah
the pressure hasn't affected there Todd
is still making her sharp
she won't be able to catch leader 92
points ahead that's gonna still give her
a chance
mrs. Tanya and even Georgia will have a
chance on that final round Great Falls
dive couch looking to stay within
touching distance and she does 72 marks
takes it to two eight five five oh that
means she's just over 20 points behind
Lully apricot shook with one round of
diving in this ten meter final to go so
put a cop took the defending champion
leads and she's got a handy cushion
ahead of capture more the two Brits in
second and third one round then left to
come on one round of real drama I'm sure
in store for us here in London
well we teed this competition up at the
start of the evening as potential drama
and it's exactly what we've got last
round to dive set in the women's ten
meter final at this 2016 European
Championship so like Kalonji 18 year old
from Paris has given a really good
account of herself this to sign off
there no medal tonight for a light but
it's a really good performance and she's
been solid tonight she really has she
has a unique sound to her entries it's
not even quite a tearing sound it's just
strange isn't it but it's medicine
rising so clearly she's not experienced
as the other drivers but she looks quite
poetic with her dives anyway and then
you get this really strange silence
sound on the entry
[Music]
moves to two seven nine 304 Kalonji
and that's really good work from the 18
year old great experience compadre at
Laura Marano has already experienced a
silver medal at these championships back
in 2015 but for her today it just hasn't
quite happened so back and forth at the
moment meaning this back to and half
somersaults with one and a half twists
has to be the best that she can make it
and if she can get up into the high 70s
80s maybe there's a chance
oh no just very short yeah when she was
on the platform the arms didn't swing up
over her head she looked very rigid here
and then going forward into the pipe
after the twist it just too low to the
water yeah very slow on the somersault
she tried to stay into the plaque as
long as she could but couldn't get
around to the vertical position she was
nine points behind Georgia who was in
third place at the end of Round four
after her full five rounds of diving
she's only eight points ahead of bukata
who's had four rounds so that puts it
into context it's unlikely to be a medal
for Moreno this evening
Genevieve green angelahr then of
Lithuania the 17-year old still smiling
the crowd of responded really well to
she's had a torrid time tonight started
off in the first round poorly that's
knocked her confidence and just wants an
entry in this final dive and she's got
it at last
well down to Genevieve and genomic yeah
the high score she's had at this point
was 43 she's got a 33 and 19 and then
the 8 but finally this is a dive there's
worthy of the European Championship good
jump
lovely Pike there locks out it's a shame
it's a low degree of difficulty and
they'll go more than 43 points but they
can't take away from her is the fact
that she's finished 12th in a European
Championship and that's something
certainly to brag about so and genomic
signs off with a good one same vine
doing we'll want to be doing the same
best finish that she's had in this
competition was last year and that was a
9th place so a good dive here and she
could improve on that qualified in
Knights came 9th last year and she's in
nights at the moment back two and a half
then for Celine
it's a nice finish but she keeps
throwing up that plume of splash when
she goes through the water yeah that's
cool it's not because of the take-off
this is good the pike is good but she
just doesn't reach back enough with
their hands it's almost like a shoulders
are too tired its left and to get the
arms back there needs to be reaching
back there doesn't do that the arms are
in front of the ears and the body just
collapses a little bit 56 5 5 then for
van doing that and the clunk you heard
on the microphone then that is fico
commentator kris know basically
demonstrating everything he talks about
it's an animated commentary box I can
tell you I'm like the Italians are they
had a good week the Italians and there
might still get better as well with del
a pain can yato to go in the 3 metre
synchro later this week now back to this
competition that's nicely to sign off
for Ukraine she's had a side night this
evening
no bad takeoff did find that entry where
did that come from
who's like there's oil on me into the
diving board that she just slipped off
she didn't get any jump just slides
there kicks good though and the entry
spines will help
well she can get now and start better
the judges won't be marking her down
there'll be a 70 pointer the entry they
will get still some good scores
64 for zero for Hannah Cross nicely to
finish off and acknowledges the applause
from the crowd some of that applause
very definitely directed towards this
young one a Georgia Ward then another
big moment for her already had one big
moment in the team competition diving
for that bronze medal and this is a
chance of another medal right here in
word three and a half somersaults in the
tuck position at 3.2 to post a score for
a medal no it's a Miss I'm afraid for
Award I tell you what though she might
still go ahead of Moreno a good tuck
just a little slow hesitating coming out
to kick over everything's good at this
point but out too late
and hits and three 2505 she does get
past laura marano of france to lead for
the moment twenty five is still a good
snore bad key with her final dive she
has not performed well this evening but
unbelievably just standing fifth
position
is there something for her still to be
had from this competition three point to
the degree of difficulty for this back
twister if she hits it she can score big
and that's not going to do it
she made it 74 points to go ahead of
Georgia Ward's haven't any chance of a
medal doesn't get the jump leans back
I'm very sure
Peter Park wobbling around that's a poor
last eye for her just you've got to get
that jump up off the tower she just
hasn't had that she she hasn't had that
snap this evening 308 four zero so third
position at the moment George award of
Great Britain still leads on 325 oh five
with three or four challenges still in
the mixed and consolation peck on the
cheek there from mum for now Amy back
key Katarina Patrick over sixth position
she at least record a score to ask some
questions here she would have to go
nines to go ahead of George award to get
81 points oh wow is that back twister
worth nines Chris on finals night it's
not worth nines maybe an eighth the
jumps good very fast twists too much to
go any higher than the night technically
good yeah she doesn't get the final lock
out maybe 70s well judges agree with you
just the one eight in there seven and a
half's for 72 three 16:05 so perchick
over finishes up behind george award and
ward moving ever closer to a medal
hurry up that one miss in the last round
let's basically cost her everything back
twister then two-and-a-half somersaults
with one and a half twists in the pike
position at 3.2 but she too would have
to go near to the maximum she would need
nines and maybe one nine and a half to
get to 325 which is what George Awards
on now it doesn't get a jump finishes
blow the board on that first one half
twist doesn't finish extending the legs
on the jump opening the pike and ducks
ahead down on the entry award has seen
another challenger for a medal off Corzo
was one of the danger women in this draw
he's below 300 and that's below par way
below par for her so Maria Cujo signs
off
three more to come
and well lassen has got a find a
phenomenal score and mathematically it
may not even be possible well nines
Chris snowed is saying nines for us and
if she wants to get close to George
Awards score for a bronze medal it's a
good dive it's a really good effort but
again it's not gonna be enough now that
little movement on the end will keep it
down to seven laughs maybe a knight
again just too much moving over she
watching on the replay just legs a
little bit I think she's gone well you
can hear those scores in the background
you can multiply that against the 3.2
and what it means is that George award
is going to take a medal away from this
European Championship final the color
will be decided by the next two divers
so us and signs off with 310 scored and
rakaat Chuck takes a big deep breath
from her point of view this back twister
is all about shutting the door on the
rest so to move into top spot she
doesn't have to do too much she just has
to perform a fifth dive quite
beautifully and that's probably gold I
tell you what I reckon she's gonna break
the European record as three
73.3 that she set in 2013
that is a really good call Chris and she
thoroughly deserves it that's five
rounds of cracking diving from pro kata
she's gonna smash the record certainly
she's gonna get more than 68 points
apricot jerk looks like she's defending
her title to make it five goals and a
new European record at 385 nine Oh pro
Katja reigning supreme here in this Paul
now that would have got her a bronze
medal at the Olympic Games
Wow well that's what everybody's looking
for against the rest of the world in Rio
and pro culture will go there in great
form couch then still diving for a medal
and that'll do it
brilliant dive from Tonya couch and the
celebration under the water tells you
all you need to know she's done it she's
got her medal at last and what a way to
do it
she's got tens on this dive before not
quite a turn because it's a loss flashy
look how high she finishes she just
continues to float down from 7 meters
this is her favorite diet that's why
she's got it here in round number 5 it's
a reliable one was promised you we
promised you were good and to start the
evening we've got a new European record
we've got two medals for Great Britain
Tonya couch at the expense of her
compatriot George award claims the
silver but George award will be
delighted with her second medal at this
Europeans but hats off to Lully apricot
took that new record of 385 nine oh he's
right up there with the rest of the
world and it's the defence of her title
to make it 5 10 meter gold medals for
her and for Ukraine
brilliant performance Prakash Chuck it's
the champion